A Guide to the Records of George Bernard Lorraine, ca. 1925-1976
Library of Virginia
- Real estate records (Box 1-149)
  - Virginia real estate (Box 1-146)
    - Northumberland County (Box 108-119)
      - Edwards, Clarence: 26 acres, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 16)
      - Eubank, A.R.: 1/2 acre, 1956 (Box 113, Folder 17)
      - Fisher, Mr.: 8 acres, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 18)
      - Fitchett, T. Vaden: 1956 (Box 113, Folder 19)
      - Fleeton, Thomas: n.d. (Box 113, Folder 20)
      - Frye, Mr.: 10 acres, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 1)
      - Gamble, Robert A.: 8 3/4 acres, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2)
      - Garner, David S.: 2 acres, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      - Gayle, Mr.: 1 acre, 1956 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      - Gibson, J.H.: 1965-1966 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - Gold, Douglas: 74 acres, 1965-1972 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - Goodman, Clem: 1957 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - Green, R.L.: 2 3/4 acres, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Haislip, Mr.: 1972 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - Hall, Raymond C.: 2 acres, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - Harding, Mr.: 1 acre, 1960 (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - Harding, Franklin L.: 68 acres, 1942-1944 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      - Hayne, Juin: 30 acres, 1947 (Box 114, Folder 13)
      - Hazzard, Vernon: 1955 (Box 114, Folder 14)
      - Heath, Mrs.: 63 acres, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 15)
      - Herring, George R.: 6 3/4 acres, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 16)
      - Hinton, Mr.: 29 acres, 1958 (Box 114, Folder 17)
      - Hinton, Ira D.: 1945 (Box 114, Folder 18)
      - Hoge, William A.: 12 acres, 1947 (Box 114, Folder 19)
      - Hudson, Harry G.: 44 acres, 1942-1943 (Box 115, Folder 1)
      - Hudson, Harry G.: 50 acres, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      - Hughes, Mrs.: 1958 (Box 115, Folder 3)
      - Hughes, Elsie: 3 acres, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 4)
      - Hughes, Richard: 1950 (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - Hull, M.: 1/2 acre, 1956 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - Hutchings, T.W.: 59 acres, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 7)
      - James, Arthur: 1957 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      - Jenkins, Mr.: 1957 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      - Jett, Mr.: 1958 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      - Jones, Paul: 1957 (Box 115, Folder 11)
      - Keane, Carter M.: 1943-1958 (Box 115, Folder 12)
      - Keck, Frederick M.: 1964-1965 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      - Kennedy, Patrick D.: 1962 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - Kerr, Mr.: 1962 (Box 115, Folder 15)
      - King, Firmadge: 1949 (Box 115, Folder 16)
      - Krentz, H.M.: 1933 (Box 115, Folder 17)
      - Lankford, W.S.: 20 acres, 1943 (Box 116, Folder 1)
      - Lester, G.R.: 1 3/4 acres, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      - Lilly, P.E.: 13 acres, 1936 (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - Lumpkin, R.H.: 5 acres, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - McAllister, D.F.: 138 acres, 1945-1948 (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - McNamara, James H.: 7 acres, 1965 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - McNeal, H.P.: 14 acres, 1945 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - Marsh, Mr.: 1967 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - Marshall, Etta B.: 100 acres, 1939 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      - Mead, Norman: 2 acres, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      - Metcalf, Lillian: 1959 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      - Miles, W.A.: 12 acres, 1948 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      - Mitchell, D.T.: 38 acres, 1947 (Box 116, Folder 13)
      - Murphy, Mr.: 7 acres, 1960 (Box 116, Folder 14)
      - Northern, Byers: 2 acres, 1950 (Box 116, Folder 15)
      - Norvell, Caskie: 20 acres, 1941 (Box 116, Folder 16)
      - Olmstead, Gerard: 1947-1948 (Box 116, Folder 17)
      - Peoples Bank of Reedville: 18 acres, 1937-1938 (Box 116, Folder 18)
      - Percival, Mrs.: 2 acres, 1958 (Box 116, Folder 19)
      - Peverly, S.D.: 471 acres, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 20)
      - Pittman, Leonard: 20 acres, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 21)
      - Powell, Ralph T.: 2 1/2 acres, 1960 (Box 116, Folder 22)
      - Preston, Mr.: 10 acres, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - Reed, F.C.: 15 acres, 1960 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      - Reedy, George C.: 335 acres, 1958 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      - Richardson, J.D.: 1961 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - Richardson, W.P.: 29 acres, 1949 (Box 117, Folder 5)
      - Rittenhouse, Bette C.: 1964 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      - Rogers, M.L.: 1960 (Box 117, Folder 7)
      - Rose, Eugene: 13 acres, 1960 (Box 117, Folder 8)
      - Rutledge, C.W.: 1966 (Box 117, Folder 9)
      - Ryder, Mary S.: 4 acres, 1959-1960 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      - Sadtler, Mr.: 1947 (Box 117, Folder 11)
      - Sadtler, Edward H.: 9 acres, 1943-1956 (Box 117, Folder 12)
      - Sandy, Robert B.: 1960 (Box 117, Folder 13)
      - Sanford, Mrs.: 2 acres, 1962 (Box 117, Folder 14)
      - Smith, Charles H.: 120 acres, 1949 (Box 117, Folder 15)
      - Smith, Marston H.: 1957-1958 (Box 117, Folder 16)
      - Spence, Mrs.: 400 acres, 1949 (Box 117, Folder 17)
      - Spence, William S.: 400 acres, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Stephens, Henry S.: 2 1/2 acres, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Stern, Dorothy: 1 acre, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - Stokes, Collin: 10 acres, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Swing, Mrs.: 1947 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Tarrant, George: 65 acres, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Thomas, Basil: 1 acre, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Thomas, William G.: 1958-1963 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - Tignor, J.C.: 50 acres, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - Thrift, Elwood: 3/4 acres, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 10)
      - Tunner, William H.: 45 acres, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 11)
      - Van Derburgh, Mr.: 30 acres, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 12)
      - Viall, Clyde: 1955-1959 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      - Vinson, Helen: 170 acres, 1942-1954 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      - Wagensellar, A.W.: 70 acres, 1946-1951 (Box 118, Folder 15)
      - Walker, Mr.: 1961 (Box 118, Folder 16)
      - Walker, Henry: 1963 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      - Watkins, F.V.: 1967-1971 (Box 118, Folder 18)
      - Watkins, Grover: 1972 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      - Watson, J. Otis: 20 acres, 1949-1950 (Box 119, Folder 2)
      - Whaley, Roland: 2 acres, 1952-1957 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      - Whaley, Willard B.: 20 acres, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      - Windle, William F.: 10 acres, 1957-1959 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      - Wise, Jack: 37 acres, 1964 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      - Witt, H.K.: 1 acre, 1961 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      - Woodroof, Bill: 6 acres, 1965 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      - Yetter, W.R.: 156 acres, 1948 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified home in Fleeton: 1965-1966 (Box 119, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified home in Heathsville: 1958 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified home in Mantua: 1957 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1975 (Box 119, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 119, Folder 14-15)
    - Nottoway County (Box 120)
      - Blackstone Military Academy: J.H. Clay, 1948 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - Burkville Dairy Farm: Mr. Boswell, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - Crewe Hotel: Ray Houchen, 1949 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      - Fair Oaks Farm: Jerry C. Stroup, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      - Hyde Park: George V. Scott, 1936-1949 (Box 120, Folder 5)
      - Miracle Brothers Dairy Farm: 325 acres, 1952 (Box 120, Folder 6)
      - Oakwood Farm: W.A. Smiley, 1953-1955 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      - Olds Farm: L.H. Garrett, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 8)
      - Rose Hill: Charles H. Wilson, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 9)
      - Roseland: W.D. Dickinson, 1942 (Box 120, Folder 10)
      - Southall's Dairy Farm: R.E. Southall, 1953-1954 (Box 120, Folder 11)
      - Bass, Mr.: 10 acres, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 12)
      - Hamlett, H.R.: 1949 (Box 120, Folder 13)
      - Watkins, Thomas R.: 1957 (Box 120, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Orange County (Box 121-123)
      - Achnacarry: 160 acres, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Barboursville: John B. Gordon, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - Briary Farm: Joseph M. Samuels, 1948-1966 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - Brookdale: Joseph M. Samuels, 1937 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - Burlington: D.D. Ball, 1943-1944 (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - Chestnut Hill: Federal Land Bank of Baltimore, 1930-1936 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - Cleethrow Farm: William A. Rudasill, 1933-1936 (Box 121, Folder 7)
      - Conistone: Charles E. Hall, 1937-1938 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - Conistone Farm: Shiras A. Blair, 1948-1968 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - Gaston Hall: William R. Scharton, 1938-1942 (Box 121, Folder 10)
      - Glen Cove: O.T. Funkhouse, 1943 (Box 121, Folder 11)
      - Glendale Farm: Kate M. Brooking, 1949 (Box 121, Folder 12)
      - Green Level: R.M. Carpenter, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 13)
      - Greenwood: K.S. Edwards, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 14)
      - Hampstead: Mr. Barbour, 1930's (Box 121, Folder 15)
      - Hare Forest: J.S. Gregory, 1945 (Box 121, Folder 16)
      - Hawfield: Stuart M. Lewis, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 17)
      - Hawfield: John S. Rixey, 1936, 1947-1952 (Box 121, Folder 18)
      - Hazelhurst: Eleanor R. Nalle, 1937-1954 (Box 121, Folder 19)
      - Huntsmen's Rest: L.E. Burlingame, 1941-1951 (Box 121, Folder 20)
      - Linden: Lucy A. Bennett, 1935 (Box 121, Folder 21)
      - Linden: Jack Samuels, 1971 (Box 121, Folder 22)
      - Malbone: F.H. Schroeder, 1950 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Montebello: 190 acres, 1945 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Monteith: John Cowherd, 1937 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Mount Sharon: R.C. Slaughter, 1935 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Mount Sharon: Ellsworth H. Augustus, 1946-1951 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Mount Valley Farm: R.J. Crockett, 1953 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Milford Dairy Farms: Joseph M. Samuels, 1949-1952 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Morton Hall: L.C. Knapp, 1949 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Piedmont: Egbert Leigh, 1942-1953 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - Routon Grange: Maud Farrer, 1935 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - Somerset: A.H. Jones, 1937-1938 (Box 122, Folder 11)
      - Springfield: Cabell King, 1936-1938 (Box 122, Folder 12)
      - Tetley Farm: Rosa Kile, 1942 (Box 122, Folder 13)
      - Tillinghass: Joseph M. Samuels, 1955 (Box 122, Folder 14)
      - Tivoli: 235 acres, 1938, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 15)
      - Tobacco House Farm: Joseph M. Samuels, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 16)
      - Walnut Hills: E. Irving Eldredge, 1933-1945 (Box 122, Folder 17)
      - Waverly Farm: Joseph M. Samuels, 1954 (Box 122, Folder 18)
      - Willow Grove: H.O. Tyne, 1933-1941 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - Aljan, Abraham: 212 1/2 acres, 1955 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - Guthrie, J.C.: 1953 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - Huffman, E.V.: 370 acres, 1938 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - Kean, B.L.: 183 acres, 1941-1942 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - McClenny, D.C.: 100 acres, 1933 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - Niehl, Harriet W.: 6 acres, 1948 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - Samuels, Joseph M.: 10 acres, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - Samuels, Joseph M.: 1933, 1936 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - Taliaferro, Mr.: n.d. (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - Wunsch, Chester L.: 160 acres, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1955 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Page County (Box 124, Folder 1-3)
      - Shawnee Farms: Fred Rosskopf, 1945-1948 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - Julia, Miss: 1946 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Patrick County (Box 124, Folder 4-6)
      - Patrick Springs: E.B. Wallace, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933, 1948-1949, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Petersburg (Box 124, Folder 7-8)
      - Spangler Farm: Adelaide Boyd, 1930-1937 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - Cuthbert, James: 1944 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Pittsylvania County (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Powhatan County (Box 124-126)
      - Belle-Nemus: Mann S. Valentine, 1940-1941 (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - Belle-Nemus: 1968 (Box 124, Folder 11)
      - Calais: D.L. Turpin, 1936-1940 (Box 124, Folder 12)
      - Calais: O.C. Britton, 1964 (Box 124, Folder 13)
      - Colona: E.W. Henning, 1937-1941 (Box 124, Folder 14)
      - Colona: Joseph A. Dart, 1947-1950 (Box 124, Folder 15)
      - Fighting Creek: 1968 (Box 124, Folder 16)
      - Glebe: W.F. Wade, 1952-1954 (Box 124, Folder 17)
      - Glendale: Wilton R. Johnson, 1942 (Box 124, Folder 18)
      - Grassland Farm: Edward T. Janney, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 19)
      - Hunter's Fare: T.S. Curtis, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - Indian Camp: Charles Simpson, 1937-1939 (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - Keswick: G.C. Kirkmeyer, 1937-1941 (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Keswick: Elam & Funsten, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Malvern: E.M. Archer, 1935 (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Manakin Farm: H.R. Pettus, 1936-1944 (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - Morewood: Paul H. Bock, 1952-1953 (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - Oak Forest: O.L. Dobson, 1941 (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - Old Arsenal: Florence M. Smith, 1934 (Box 125, Folder 9)
      - Old Jefferson Landing: C.W. Johnson, 1949 (Box 125, Folder 10)
      - Olmstead Dairy Farm: G.D. Olmstead, 1949-1950 (Box 125, Folder 11)
      - Paxton: John H. Karrh, 1937-1954 (Box 125, Folder 12)
      - Spring Garden Farm: P.N. Brauer, 1951-1952 (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - Stonehenge Farm: Allen Saville, 1943 (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - Vinita: Laura Williams, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Windsor: Fred I. Hobbs, 1950 (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - Woodlawn: Mr. Hopkins, 1950 (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - Armentrout, Mr.: 1940 (Box 126, Folder 6)
      - Brauer, P.N.: 250 acres, 1941 (Box 126, Folder 7)
      - Franck, Stanley: 21 acres, 1945-1946 (Box 126, Folder 8)
      - Green, W.E.: 255 acres, 1952-1954 (Box 126, Folder 9)
      - Hening, J. Hamilton: 235 acres, 1938 (Box 126, Folder 10)
      - Inge, Ruby C.: 396 acres, 1965 (Box 126, Folder 11)
      - Jones, Robert R.: 1950 (Box 126, Folder 12)
      - Nicholls, J.W.: 135 acres, 1938 (Box 126, Folder 13)
      - Perkins, Harry: 240 acres, 1941 (Box 126, Folder 14)
      - Rolf, A.G.: 215 acres, 1934-1935 (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - Scott, Samuel: 190 acres, 1940 (Box 126, Folder 16)
      - Tilman, L.H.: 175 acres, 1941 (Box 126, Folder 17)
      - Tuck, J.R.: 315 acres, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1938 (Box 126, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1940 (Box 126, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Prince Edward County (Box 127, Folder 1-5)
      - Linden: J.S. Shackleton, 1957 (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - Rotherwood: T.F. Johnson, 1942-1950 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Rotherwood: F.W. Shanaberger, 1951-1954 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - Lancaster, A.H.: 54 acres, 1958 (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - McEvoy, W.H.: 2 acres, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Prince George County (Box 127-129)
      - Aberdeen Farm: Edward A. Marks, 1937-1941 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - Beaver Castle: R.E. Hite, 1936-1937 (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - Evergreen: Harry C. Thompson, 1948 (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - Flower de Hundred: J. Roland Rooke, 1937-1951 (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - Fort Powhatan: Fred R. Shepherd, 1931-1943 (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - Maycocks: Norwood Wilson, 1934-1942 (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - Powell Creek Farm: Andrew Balint, 1942-1943 (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - River Edge Farm: Gill Realty Company, 1942 (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - Tar Bay: G.C. Ruffin, 1942 (Box 127, Folder 14)
      - Upper Brandon: H.C. Thompson, 1959-1960 (Box 127, Folder 15)
      - Upper Brandon: photographs (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - Upper Brandon: photographs (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Upper Quarter: William Stanley Burt, 1937-1941 (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Willow Hill: Quincy Cole, 1947-1949 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - Willow Hill: John H. Trant, 1950-1952 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Willow Hill: John H. Trant, 1961-1962 (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Willow Hill: John H. Trant, photographs (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Willow Hill: G.C. Kirkmyer, 1950-1952 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Willow Hill: photographs (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - Arnold, R.L.: 711 acres, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Carter, James Walter: n.d. (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Carter, James Walter: 1948-1960 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - Cutchin, Mr.: 253 acres, 1951 (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - Dougherty, C.H.: 15 acres, 1971 (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - Wright, L.R.: 240 acres, 1954 (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1939 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Prince William County (Box 129, Folder 8-15)
      - Annaburg: A. Palwine, n.d. (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - Cannon Branch Dairy Farm: W.T. Secord, 1937 (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - Evergreen: R.B. Gosson, 1937 (Box 129, Folder 10)
      - Meadow Farm: B.E. Allen, 1952 (Box 129, Folder 11)
      - Stage Coach Inn: Robert L. Garrison, 1957 (Box 129, Folder 12)
      - Herring, G.W.: 640 acres, 1945 (Box 129, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1938, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Princess Anne County (Box 130)
      - Croatan Club: 1933-1939 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Graygate: E.M. Patterson, 1934-1938 (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - Crockett, J.S.: 117 acres, 1946 (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - Earl, Paul D.: 1953-1954 (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - Lyle, J. Lawrence: 90 acres, 1950 (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Parker, Mr.: 1 acre, 1960 (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Withers, J.B.: 4 acres, 1948 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1961 (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1934-1940 (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Rappahannock County (Box 131, Folder 1-22)
      - Blankenbaker: Hening and Pillar (Brokers), 1953 (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Bruce Farm: Hening, 1949 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - Jessamine Hill: F.W. Sharp, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - Laurel Hill: Mr. Hughes, 1949 (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - Meadow Green: Miss Fink, 1949 (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - Mountain Green: John J. Miller, 1933-1939 (Box 131, Folder 6)
      - Mount Ida: S.E. Hening, 1952 (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - Pleasant Hill: S.E. Hening, 1955 (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - Quaintance Farm: S.E. Hening, 1949 (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - Red Hill: William Brooking, 1941 (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - Ricketts Hotel: Mr. Hening, 1949 (Box 131, Folder 11)
      - Shade Farm: Charles King, 1950 (Box 131, Folder 12)
      - Woodlawn: C.R. Wood, 1933-1941 (Box 131, Folder 13)
      - Hening, Mrs.: 1949 (Box 131, Folder 14)
      - Hening, S.E.: 1960 (Box 131, Folder 15)
      - Menefee, Carroll: 1949 (Box 131, Folder 16)
      - Pillar, T.J.: 2645 acres, 1960 (Box 131, Folder 17)
      - Pillar, T.J.: 532 acres, 1962 (Box 131, Folder 18)
      - Wirtz, Mr.: 230 acres, 1949 (Box 131, Folder 19)
      - Wood, W.H.: 346 acres, 1941 (Box 131, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1939, 1950 (Box 131, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Richmond (City) (Box 131-132)
      - Bon Harbours: Bill Woodruff, 1964 (Box 131, Folder 23)
      - Bowman Building: Louis O. Bowman, 1954 (Box 131, Folder 24)
      - Pittaway Farm: John Connor, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 25)
      - Walford Hotel: W.P. Melton, 1945 (Box 131, Folder 26)
      - Braddock, Mrs.: 1954 (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - Sanders, Mrs.: 1947 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Stradley, Kenneth N.: 1955 (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Williams, Langbourne: 1930's (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1939, 1945 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Richmond County (Box 132-133)
      - Belle Mount Farm: Howard W. Reisinger, 1948-1949 (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - Carters Wharf: H.W. Coates, 1943 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - Edge Hill: Northern Neck State Bank, 1937-1946 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - Grove Mount: Dabney Overton, 1966 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - Indian Banks: Robert A. Gamble, 1933-1949 (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - Ingleside: S.R. Hopkins, 1946 (Box 132, Folder 12)
      - Milden Hall: Ely Sharp, 1933 (Box 132, Folder 13)
      - Milden Hall: A. Russell Council, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 14)
      - Rainbow Orchard: Judge Shackelford, 1942 (Box 132, Folder 15)
      - Shandy Hall: Fred Durham, 1938-1961 (Box 132, Folder 16)
      - Wilna: George H. Rosa, 1939-1950 (Box 132, Folder 17)
      - Woodberry: D.E. Foster, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 18)
      - Barton, Charles K.: 1960 (Box 132, Folder 19)
      - Coates, Mr.: 20 acres, 1933 (Box 132, Folder 20)
      - Foster, O.L.: 4 acres, 1943 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Gallagher, Eileen B.: 1956-1957 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Hayden, Richard: 1956 (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Lewis, Mr.: 1941 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - McMackin, John W.: 1947 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Maucos, George E.: 1962 (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Northern Neck State Bank: 63 acres, 1937 (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Packett, R.C.: 267 acres, 1938 (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Payne, W.W.: 2 acres, 1933-1942 (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - Payne, W.W.: 87 acres, 1942 (Box 133, Folder 10)
      - Pointer, W.H.: 1937-1947 (Box 133, Folder 11)
      - Ratcliffe, Mr.: 312 acres, 1941 (Box 133, Folder 12)
      - Ratcliffe, Harold: 53 acres, 1944-1953 (Box 133, Folder 12)
      - Revere, Paul: 1 1/4 acres, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 14)
      - Schools, G.B.: 200 acres, 1937-1938 (Box 133, Folder 15)
      - Self, E.H.: 100 acres, 1958 (Box 133, Folder 16)
      - Smith, Harvey C.: 1957-1958 (Box 133, Folder 17)
      - Sanders, J.J.: 1955 (Box 133, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1940 (Box 133, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 133, Folder 20)
    - Roanoke (City) (Box 133, Folder 21-23)
      - Fielder Building: J.W. Elliott, 1950 (Box 133, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1956 (Box 133, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 133, Folder 23)
    - Rockbridge County (Box 134, Folder 1-5)
      - Settledown: T.S. Settle, 1946 (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Rockbridge Alum Springs: Harold H. Bailey, 1944 (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Roberson, C.W.: 95 acres, 1956 (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Winfree, P.B.: 801 acres, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Rockingham County (Box 134-135)
      - Court Manor: R.J. Funkhauser, 1952 (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - Court Manor: Canning Land Company, 1960 (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Gables Hotes: Stewart Huston, 1946 (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Marshall Hotel: Wilbur P. Anthony (realtor) (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - Showker Brothers building: Bessie S. Abdallah, 1950 (Box 134, Folder 10)
      - Anthony, Wilbur P.: 1950 (Box 134, Folder 11)
      - Clower, R.J.: 640 acres, 1962 (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - Dean, William: 14 acres, 1944 (Box 134, Folder 13)
      - Foster, E.M.: 1948 (Box 134, Folder 14)
      - Klingstein, E.L.: 365 acres, 1948 (Box 134, Folder 15)
      - Leonard, Floyd: 630 acres, 1950 (Box 134, Folder 16)
      - Roller, Mr.: 515 acres, 1944 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Parker (realtor): 1968 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Wine, Beulah L.: 350 acres, 1944 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1944-1956 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Russell County (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Shenandoah County (Box 135, Folder 7-17)
      - Battlefield Crystal Caverns: R.A. Howard, 1957-1960 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Birdwood: Philip Williams, 1944 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - Shenandoah Caverns: 1953 (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - Shenvalec Hotel and Golf Course: J.G. Miller, 1945-1954 (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Spring Valley Farm: F. Lorain Bowman, 1963 (Box 135, Folder 11)